just before we start as a background
就在我们开始作为背景之前
thing that way I won't burn some of the
这样我就不会烧掉一些
tight 45 minutes we have for lots and
紧张的45分钟，我们有很多
lots of slides anybody recognize this
很多人都知道的幻灯片
picture
图片
okay so for those of you and know that
好，对于你们这些人来说，知道
what that is cool
那很酷
anybody that hasn't seen it before when
以前没有看过的人
I guess what that is this is this is a
我想这是什么
documentation of the ultimate in duct
终极风管文件
tape engineering this is the Apollo 13
磁带工程这是阿波罗13号
co2 scrubber or you literally have a
二氧化碳洗涤器，或者您实际上有一个
square peg that needed to fit on top of
需要固定在上方的方形钉
a round hole with duct tape and
带胶带的圆孔和
engineers got to do that from hundreds
工程师必须从数百人中做到这一点
of thousands of miles away to save
千里之外保存
people's lives which is amazing it's
人们的生活是惊人的
like a truly heroic act and fact that
就像一个真正的英雄行为和事实
they got to get this stuff working
他们必须使这些东西起作用
together and figured it out
一起弄清楚
with the little things that that on a
上面的小东西
spacecraft was great but I like to use
宇宙飞船很棒，但我喜欢用
it as an example of both a truly heroic
它既是一个真正英雄的例子
act the kind of engineering we would all
采取我们都会做的那种工程
be proud to do and if you get to do
自豪地去做，如果你去做
something that cool once in a lifetime
一辈子很酷的东西
you it's amazing but it's also something
你这太神奇了，但这也是
to learn from anytime you see one of
随时随地学习
these things the main thing you should
这些东西你应该主要
be thinking is my job is to make it so
认为这是我的工作就是做到这一点
that's never needed duct tape
不需要胶带
Engineering is really cool it's a great
工程真的很棒，这很棒
skill if you can use it to save the day
技巧，如果可以用它来挽救一天
but it's mostly something that should be
但是大部分应该是
avoided and whenever you look at the
避免，只要你看着
daily things that you do that amount to
每天要做的事情等于
putting duct tape on things to make the
将胶带贴在东西上
problem go away just keep that in mind
问题消失只是记住这一点
it's a it's a useful thing to try to
尝试尝试是一件很有用的事情
avoid okay I'm gonna start with the
避免吧，我将从
actual site that we're going to talk
我们要讨论的实际站点
about java at speed focusing on modern
关于Java的速度，着重于现代
hardware what modern hardware seems to
硬件，现代硬件似乎
be and and how we get the most out of it
以及我们如何充分利用它
this will by definition be an outdated
根据定义，这将是过时的
talk in a few years because modern
谈论几年，因为现代
hardware will not be modern back then
那时的硬件将不再是现代的
but I will try and focus on some of the
但我会尝试着重于一些
cutting-edge hardware you could get your
先进的硬件，您可以获得
hands on today as a high-level agenda
今天作为高层议程来处理
we're going to do some intro motivation
我们将做一些介绍性的动机
talk about hardware transit features
谈论硬件传输功能
talk about some compiler stuff because
谈论一些编译器的东西，因为
to get actual usefulness compilers have
获得编译器的实际有用性
to do their job and we'll start with
去做他们的工作，我们将从
basics and build up from that we'll take
基础知识并以此为基础
a little detour into a micro benchmark
稍微绕开了微型基准
example and hopefully well have time for
例子，希望有时间
that then some more compiler stuff a
然后再有一些编译器的东西
little more cool compiler stuff the kind
有点酷的编译器之类的东西
of things just get to just get to do
只是要做的事情
that it's really cool and then talk a
真的很酷，然后再说
little bit about other problems on
关于其他问题的一点点
modern hardware and modern compilers
现代硬件和现代编译器
like warm up and then putting it all
喜欢热身，然后把它全部
together and maybe a little bit of
在一起，也许一点点
bragging towards then I'll try and keep
吹牛然后我会努力保持
the bragging down until then but at the
吹牛直到那时，但在
end I will break I'm Gill tena and the
最后，我要打破我是吉尔·泰纳（Gill tena），
CTO versus Oh systems we make JVMs we
CTO与Oh系统，我们制作JVM
think that the best JVM s-- on earth
认为世界上最好的JVM
I've been working on things like garbage
我一直在做垃圾
collection for about fourteen years
收藏约十四年
thirteen years
十三年
this is documentation of me actually
这实际上是我的文件
doing that that that was a trash
那样做那是垃圾
compactor in my kitchen it was broken
我厨房的压实机坏了
trash compactors are supposed to do
垃圾压实机应该做的
minor garbage collections during a week
一周内收集少量垃圾
so the full GC only happens once a week
因此完整的GC仅每周发生一次
that's what we do with Java all the time
这就是我们一直使用Java所做的
anyway here it was broken the
无论如何，它被打破了
defragmentation function wasn't working
碎片整理功能不起作用
right you can see the fragments falling
对，你可以看到碎片掉落
out the back I had to fix it and this
从后面我不得不修复它，这
was taken in 2004 was just thirteen
是在2004年拍摄的，当时只有十三岁
years ago so I really need new pictures
年前，所以我真的需要新照片
I've built a lot of stuff which means
我建造了很多东西，这意味着
I've made a lot of mistakes and I
我犯了很多错误，我
learned from some of them and I try to
从其中一些中学到的，我尝试
kind of you know tell other people about
那种你知道的告诉别人
the mistakes maybe they'll learn about
他们可能会学到的错误
them too and as all we make JVMs that
他们也一样，因为我们使JVM
focus on speed focus on latency focusing
专注于速度专注于延迟
focus on consistency so we we know about
专注于一致性，所以我们知道
it some about it and and I also you know
关于它的一些，我也知道
as a side subject like to talk about
作为副主题喜欢谈论
things like how people measure things
人们如何衡量事物
and response time and latency so you can
以及响应时间和延迟，这样您就可以
find talks of mine probably online about
在网上找到有关我的谈话
rents on that subject which this is not
在那个不是这个的租金
this is about speed it's a speed what is
这是关于速度，这是速度
it good for absolutely nothing
绝对没有好处
say it again
再说一遍
but but what is it good for when we say
但是当我们说
speak what do we mean so you know how we
说我们的意思，所以你知道我们
fast are we slow that's a valid question
我们快慢是一个有效的问题
but it has to have some context so for
但是它必须要有一定的背景
example when are we fast are we fast at
例如我们什么时候快？
night when nobody's using this or when
晚上没有人使用时或
it's important are we fast for example
重要的是我们要斋戒吗
when we're rolling out new code you know
当我们推出新代码时，您知道
20 times a day are we still fast while
一天20次，我们还是快
that's happening or maybe we slow down
发生这种情况，或者我们放慢了速度
and we do go dead dead slow for 15
我们确实死了很慢15
minutes then everybody's happy later
分钟，然后大家都开心
what about peak times we fast when it
高峰时间怎么样呢？
really matters when when when it's Black
当什么时候是黑色真的很重要
Friday or when a market opens or you
星期五或市场开盘或您
know when things really matter when slow
知道什么时候真正重要什么时候慢
and fast are important not just on
快速不仅在
average and you know when you actually
平均，你知道你什么时候真正
do something like trading for example or
做一些交易，例如
or or buying something online
或或在线购买商品
are you fast at that point in time the
你在那个时间点快吗
other question is are you reliably fast
另一个问题是您可靠吗
so fast is really good but sometimes you
这么快真的很好但是有时候你
can be fast but very unreliable and the
可能很快，但是非常不可靠，并且
results right now that's kind of an
现在的结果有点
important thing to keep in mind really
重要的事情要牢记
really fast could be dangerous
真的快可能很危险
really really fast and then completely
真的非常快然后完全
stalled for a minute is usually not a
停滞一分钟通常不是
really good thing so we'd like speed to
真的很好，所以我们希望速度
look like this this is how we think of
看起来像这样，这就是我们的想法
speed when we say how fast are you we'd
速度，当我们说您有多快时
like to have an answer for that question
想对此问题有一个答案
but that's not the right question
但这不是正确的问题
because no reality looks like that in
因为没有现实看起来像那样
Java the reality tends to look like this
Java现实看起来像这样
speed is all over the place you start
速度无处不在
slow you go fast then you go slow then
慢，你快走，然后你慢走，然后
you go fast and go slowly and fast and
你走得快，走得又慢又快，
understanding what this fast slow
了解什么快慢
transitions are and what they made up of
过渡是由它们组成的
is one of the things we'll try and talk
是我们会尝试谈论的事情之一
about today I'll talk about the two or
关于今天，我将谈论两个或
three main things that affect it and
影响它的三个主要方面
then we'll drive into cool things about
然后我们将深入探讨
speed
速度
so speed in the Java world looks like
所以Java世界的速度看起来像
that because for example the code we
那是因为例如我们的代码
actually execute goes through an
实际执行通过
evolution we start off with slow
进化我们从慢开始
interpreted code were literally
解释的代码从字面上看
interpreting wine byte code
解释酒的字节码
from the classes and loading them and
从类中加载它们并
it's really slow then once that's warm
真的很慢，然后温暖
enough the JVM decides oh maybe I should
足够的JVM决定哦，也许我应该
do something about it it compiles it but
对它做一些事情编译它，但是
not yet fully optimized it compiles it
尚未完全优化，它将对其进行编译
with profiling code so you could learn
与分析代码，以便您可以学习
what's going on that's this green zone
这是怎么回事
it is much faster than interpreted but
它比解释的要快得多，但是
not nearly as fast as you could go and
几乎没有你能走的快
once you figure out what the code
一旦你弄清楚什么代码
actually does then you throw an actual
其实你会抛出一个实际的
optimizing JIT compiler at it and make
在它上优化JIT编译器并制作
it go fast and that's that blue code
它运行很快，那就是蓝色代码
where you hope most of your stuff is
你希望大多数东西在那里
actually running and over time you'll
实际运行，随着时间的流逝，
stabilize where most of your stuff or
稳定你大部分的东西或
hot stuff will actually be running good
热门的东西实际上将运行良好
blue code but you don't start there so
蓝色代码，但您不从那里开始
what does that mean when you look at the
当你看这是什么意思
behavior speed over time response time
行为速度随时间的响应时间
over time response time over time looks
随着时间的推移，随着时间的推移，响应时间看起来
like this because we're running this
之所以这样，是因为我们正在运行
really slow code when we start we're
当我们开始时，代码真的很慢
really slow then we start replacing that
真的很慢，然后我们开始替换它
code with faster code but not still
更快的代码但还不是
still not really really fast just better
仍然不是真的很快只是更好
than interpret it so green stuff and
而不是将其解释为绿色的东西
then eventually that blue stuff will
然后最终，蓝色的东西会
dominate and will go fast those red
占主导地位，并会迅速走红
spikes in the middle are other things
中间的尖峰是其他东西
that make us slow like pausing for
让我们慢下来，就像暂停
garbage collection pausing for the
垃圾收集暂停
optimization pausing for whatever does
优化暂停执行任何操作
happen all the time as well if we look
如果我们继续看下去
at this as speed rather than response
以这种速度而不是回应
time
时间
it's basically an inverse and it looks
它基本上是一个逆，看起来
like that you're really slow when you
像那样当你真的很慢
start that is how slow you are we're
开始那就是你有多慢我们
talking about a 30 X ratio not about a
谈论30倍的比例而不是
you know it's nice effects kind of stuff
你知道这是很好的效果的东西
then you get faster but really not
那么你会更快，但实际上没有
really that fast and then you get to go
真的那么快，然后您就可以开始了
really really fast eventually but you
最终真的非常快，但是你
have these drops to an absolute zero
这些下降到绝对零
speed all the time because you pause
因为停顿而一直加速
that's the behavior over time for speed
这就是速度的行为
in Java applications almost invariably
在Java应用程序中几乎总是
so that's just something to keep in mind
所以这只是要记住的事情
we'll get back to the picture but you
我们会回到图片，但是你
know when we look at the parts and what
知道我们什么时候看零件以及什么
we can affect which part of speed we can
我们可以影响速度的哪一部分
affect the different technologies and
影响不同的技术
different capabilities for each of them
他们每个人都有不同的能力
so let's look at what modern servers are
让我们看看什么是现代服务器
what is it that we're running on so
我们正在运行的是什么
machines were running on
机器正在运行
this is a mostly intel servers and
这主要是英特尔服务器，
talking about the server space and these
谈论服务器空间以及这些
are the last end generations of intel
是英特尔的最后一代
server chips we're right now right
我们现在使用的服务器芯片
around here skylake SP is out Brad Wells
周围的天空SP出来了Brad Wells
Brownlee has been around for a year and
布朗利已经存在一年了，
a half if you're running on a modern
如果您使用的是现代设备则需要一半
machine that was recently bought or
最近购买的机器或
you're running on the cloud on EWS or
您正在EWS或云端上运行
Google or Azure or one of the others
Google或Azure或其他之一
you're probably running on one of those
您可能正在其中之一上运行
two and if you're not you really should
两个，如果不是，那你真的应该
move to one of those two why why are you
转到这两个之一，为什么你为什么
paying for the old hardware especially
特别为旧硬件付费
in the cloud in what you have there on
在云中，您所拥有的
the right is some interesting stuff
右边是一些有趣的东西
beyond just more cores and more cache
不仅仅是更多的内核和更多的缓存
and that kind of stuff that you can
那种东西你可以
expect there are new features new CPUs
期待有新功能的新CPU
have had new features come into them
有了新功能
over the deck of the last several
在最后几个的甲板上
generations and those features can be
世代和那些功能可以
used for speed for extreme speed if
用于极限速度
they're used right if the mission if the
如果任务是
code running on them actually
实际上在它们上运行的代码
understands those features there and can
了解那里的那些功能并且可以
be used and I'll give you some examples
被使用，我会给你一些例子
of those when we look at features
这些当我们看功能时
vectorization AVX avx2
矢量化AVX avx2
and avx-512 are really cool
和avx-512真的很酷
vectorization capabilities that evolved
进化的矢量化功能
over the generations recently BMI and
最近几代人的BMI和
BMI two are Bittman emulation
BMI的两个是Bittman仿真
instructions including things like
说明包括
scattering gathering bits that are kind
散布善良的收集点
of cool and hle in TSX our Hardware
TSX的凉爽与欢乐
transactional memory features that have
具有的事务存储功能
come and now are commodity every new CPU
来了，现在每个新CPU都是商品
has them on a server using those
使用它们将它们放在服务器上
features can give a speed beyond the
功能可以提供超越
features themselves the CPUs are just
CPU本身就是功能
getting better they were already really
变得更好，他们已经真的
really good and they just keep getting
真的很好，他们只是不断
and better and better you could see some
越来越好，你可以看到一些
trends here how many instructions out of
趋势这里有多少条指令
order instructions the CPU can keep
CPU可以保留的订购说明
juggling at the same time without them
没有他们同时玩杂耍
yet completing is growing it's also it's
但完成的过程却越来越多
already been very very impressive but
已经非常非常令人印象深刻，但是
we're keep going up and up and a CPU
我们一直在不断上升，CPU
these days it's not this simple serial
这些天不是这个简单的系列
thing that's doing an instruction at a
在某处做指令的东西
time or four of those or eight of those
时间或其中的四个或八个
interleaved it's literally throwing up
交错的字面意思是吐
200 instructions in air and catching
空中捕捉200条指令
them and then when they're done and and
他们，然后当他们完成时，和
it's keeping the Chow going out
保持了松狮犬的出没
not going it's got what do we have there
不去，那里有什么
like 96 or 72 different loads
像96或72个不同的负载
outstanding in 56 different stores
在56家不同商店中表现出色
outstanding none completed out of order
尚无未完成的订单
going to the memory just to keep the
去记忆只是为了保持
pipes full and what that means is the
管道已满，这意味着
mental model of what's going on in the
发生的事情的心理模型
CPU is hard to to project because you
CPU很难投影，因为您
may think that this happens before that
可能认为这发生在那之前
but the CPU is gonna do anything it can
但CPU会做任何可以做的事
to pick up work and do it out of order
接好工作，然后按部就班
just to get the work done and that's
只是为了完成工作，那就是
where it's so big is a window that human
这么大的地方是一扇窗户
capacity to order well to it is almost
很好地订购的能力
non-existent even compilers have a hard
不存在的编译器也很难
time doing it well and you need to think
时间做得好，你需要思考
in terms of fundamentals of operations
在操作基础上
rather than how to micro optimize to CPU
而不是如何对CPU进行微优化
here are some nice pictures and how this
这是一些漂亮的图片，以及如何
stuff breaks down from a Architecture
东西从体系结构分解
point of view and some of the evolutions
观点和一些演变
of them so for example this is sort of
他们这样，例如
the front end of the data stuff we've
我们拥有的数据资料的前端
got things coming in we've got
有东西进来，我们有
schedulers going into the different
调度程序进入不同的
operations and in a cache and the rest
操作以及缓存中的其余部分
going on but we can see in evolution for
继续，但我们可以看到进化
example from a semi bridge which is a
一个半桥的例子
few generations back to Haswell where we
几代人回到Haswell
just have more bandwidth the width of
只是拥有更多的带宽
the buses are bigger the units the
巴士的单位更大
number of operations to the cache grows
缓存操作数量增加
so we get more bandwidth in there if you
因此，如果您有更多带宽
look at the actual execution units so
看一下实际的执行单位
then the helm is the oldest on the top
那么头盔是最古老的
on the bottom Sandy Bridge to has well
在桑迪桥的最下方
we get more execution units that could
我们得到了更多的执行单元
do things at the same time they're wider
同时做事更广泛
they could do wider operations CPUs do
他们可以做更广泛的操作CPU
get better over time and the caches
随着时间的流逝和缓存的不断完善
themselves have looked like this for
自己看起来像这样
quite a while where each core had about
每个核心都有相当长的一段时间
32k of exactly 30 TK of data and
总共30 TK数据中的32k
instruction caches 256 K of l2 and a
指令缓存256 K of 2和a
shared cache across all the cores
跨所有内核共享缓存
together in a socket so the more cores
一起放在一个插座中，这样更多的核心
you have the more cash you had below
你有更多的现金
that skylake SP which is the latest
最新的Skylake SP
generation you can get that right now
一代你现在就可以得到
you can run on Google Cloud engine and
您可以在Google Cloud引擎上运行
run them
运行它们
has changed that model somewhat the
已经改变了这种模式
shifts of caches have gone around
缓存转移
another huge improvement that has
另一个巨大的改进
happened fairly recently with the
最近发生在
Haswell generation is an increase in the
Haswell代的增长
TLB cache the TLB cache is a CPU cache
TLB缓存TLB缓存是CPU缓存
that keeps mappings around and up to
保持周围和最多的映射
Haswell the number of non-small page
Haswell非小页数
maps were very small in the low tens but
低几十度的地图很小
with as well and broad well and skylake
与以及广泛的井和天空
we now have thousands of entries to
我们现在有成千上万的条目
cache two megabyte page mappings which
缓存两个兆字节的页面映射
means that the concurrently cached
表示并发缓存
mappings for virtual memory as have gone
虚拟内存的映射已经消失了
up by multiple orders of magnitude so
上升了多个数量级
finally we can actually access a large
最终我们实际上可以访问大
heap and data and not thrash the TLB and
堆和数据，而不破坏TLB和
misson in all time that's a huge step
一直以来，密森都迈出了巨大的一步
between Ivy Bridge and Haswell and it
在常春藤桥和哈斯韦尔之间
hasn't been talked about a lot but we
没被谈论很多，但是我们
can see it in results especially on
可以在结果中看到它，特别是在
large datasets
大型数据集
looking at the apology just how do these
看着道歉，这些怎么做
come together most of the servers you
汇集大多数服务器
will end up running on look like this
最终会像这样运行
two sockets with multiple cores on each
两个插槽，每个插槽上有多个内核
and memory controllers on each
和每个上的内存控制器
interconnected between the two sockets
两个插座之间互连
with some high-speed qpi or other kind
带有一些高速qpi或其他种类的
of interconnect each of the sockets has
每个插座的互连
cores and cash on them if we look at an
如果我们看一个核心
example of a specific one you look at
您要查看的特定示例
the cores they're sitting in there and
他们坐在那里的核心
the socket on this high-speed ring the
高速环上的插座
caches are localized to each coin in a
缓存被本地化为
distributed common cache around the ring
环周围的分布式通用缓存
that's a nice default you to think of if
这是一个很好的默认值，您可以考虑一下
you think of a socket has a bunch of
你想到一个插座有一堆
course shared key on the ring well
当然在环上共用钥匙
that's no longer a valid model because
这不再是有效的模型，因为
that used to be good after certain
过去肯定是好的
number of course but we just can you
当然可以，但是我们可以
know fit that many cores on a ring
知道合适，戒指上有很多芯
anymore so now we're looking like this
不再那么所以我们现在看起来像这样
they're multiple rings on a single
它们在一个环上是多个环
socket to get from one socket to the l3
从一个插座到L3的插座
cache on the same socket you might be
在同一个套接字上缓存
crossing a harp and doing all kinds of
过竖琴，做各种
other thing in fact you can configure
实际上，您可以配置其他东西
this today with configurations that say
今天的配置说
treat this is one symmetric flat socket
对待这是一个对称的扁平插座
or was something called cluster and I
或者是所谓的集群，我
that says this is like two separate
那说这就像两个分开的
sockets a new mono Darren in window
在窗口中插入新的Mono Darren
they're half the cache each but we don't
他们每个都是缓存的一半，但我们不
cross this interconnect between them
跨越他们之间的这种联系
because it's higher latency you can
因为它有更高的延迟
configure that at the bias level should
配置偏差级别
you probably not if you really
如果你真的不，你可能不会
understand if you don't really
了解你是否真的不是
understand it well but four people are
很好理解，但是四个人
fine-tuning latency performance want to
想要微调延迟性能
get every every ounce of performance out
发挥每一分的性能
of it these are things to keep in mind
这些是要记住的事情
now the other thing to keep in mind is
现在要记住的另一件事是
this is a full socket it's got all this
这是一个完整的插座
all the cores but you have options you
所有的核心，但您有选择
can buy eight eight cores 12 cores 14 16
可以买八八核12核14 16
18 24 sometimes you buy this you buy one
18 24有时候你买这个，你买一个
and a half rings like it's not actually
像是不是真的响了一半
that all the cars are built equal the
所有汽车的制造都相等
ones that are built equal the one are
那些等于一个的是
certain sizes the ones in the middle
某些尺寸在中间
often have that kind of happen too now
现在也经常发生这种情况
with skylake this picture with the ring
与天空之湖带环的这张照片
also changed dramatically you can see
你也看到了巨大的变化
the previous architectures on the Left
左侧的先前架构
skylake shifted to a mesh architecture
Skylake转向网状架构
on the chip it's sort of a 2d matrix
在芯片上有点像二维矩阵
where rather than a ring you kind of go
你去哪里而不是环
down a matrix of interconnects that look
向下看似互连的矩阵
like that and in and that's kind of an
像那样，在那种情况下
interesting level and you can sort of
有趣的水平，你可以
see what what a small tent core thing
看看什么是小帐篷的核心东西
looks like in a larger 18 core thing
看起来像是18个更大的核心
looks like down there these are all
看起来像在那边，这些都是
stuff you can find from you know all
您可以找到的东西都知道
kinds of articles about micro
关于微信的各种文章
architecture for skylake and Broadwell
Skylake和Broadwell的体系结构
and things online so that's a little
和网上的东西，这有点
context and the stuff we're running on
上下文以及我们正在运行的内容
now let's go a little lower and if you
现在让我们降低一点，如果
like machine code you're gonna really
就像机器代码一样
enjoy this if you don't like looking at
如果您不喜欢看，请享受
machine code take a deep breath this
机器代码深呼吸一下
won't take very long
不会花很长时间
okay promise won't hurt I like to look
好吧，诺言不会伤害我喜欢看的
at the actual instructions we asked the
根据实际指示，我们要求
CPUs to do and play with them and see
CPU一起玩耍并观看
what's going on because we have all
这是怎么回事，因为我们都有
these different CPUs the really cool
这些不同的CPU真的很酷
thing about a JIT is it can choose to
关于准时制的事情是它可以选择
optimize for the CPU it's actually
针对实际的CPU进行优化
running on there wasn't binary code that
运行在没有二进制代码，
was shipped beforehand so dedicated JVM
预先发货，所以专用的JVM
it can run on older hardware newer newer
它可以在较旧的硬件上运行
newer hardware and it could generate
较新的硬件，它可能会产生
different instructions for each so let's
每个都有不同的说明，所以让我们
see what actually goes on when we do
看看我们做什么时实际发生了什么
that so when i zoom into machine code I
这样，当我放大机器代码时
use a feature of zing that's that I
使用zing的功能就是
think is really cool it's kind of built
认为真的很酷，它是内置的
in
在
profiler you can basically if you put
分析器，基本上，如果您把
your code in hot loops like here I've
您的代码在像我这样的热循环中
got several benchmarks and loops I can
我有几个基准和循环
pop up a web-based screen and see how
弹出基于网络的屏幕，看看如何
much time I'm spending in each I can
我花了很多时间
click on one of those and see the actual
单击其中之一，然后查看实际
machine instructions look like that
机器指令看起来像
that's very readable right
这是非常可读的权利
I could go figure out what each
我可以去弄清楚每个
instruction does and how that maps to my
指令的功能以及它如何映射到我的
code it's kind of hard to do
编写代码有点困难
here's code this is Java code this is an
这是代码，这是Java代码，这是
actual loop and a benchmark that you
实际循环和基准
know we're summing an array just a
知道我们对一个数组求和
simple sum everything in an array and
简单地将数组中的所有内容相加，
here's the code that that generates now
这是现在生成的代码
this in itself is not very readable I
这本身不是很可读
don't try to read that a really cool
不要试图读一个很酷的东西
reason that I use a profiler to read
我使用探查器读取的原因
code is that the profile also tells me
代码是个人资料还告诉我
where I'm spending time and you see
我在那里度过时光，你会看到
those percents on the side that's the
在那边的那些百分比
code I care about
我关心的代码
it's the code that actually takes time
这实际上是需要时间的代码
since the the little percents on the
由于上的小百分比
site tell me I'm executing that code now
网站告诉我我现在正在执行该代码
I know that's the actual loop everything
我知道这是实际的循环
else is crud I don't really need to read
否则我真的不需要阅读
it it's entering the loop exiting the
它正在进入循环并退出
loop doing with exceptional conditions
在特殊条件下循环执行
that's not important that's the loop and
循环是不重要的
what we can see here this is on a
我们在这里看到的是
relatively old Westmere processor with
相对较旧的Westmere处理器
128-bit vectorized SOC and what we can
128位矢量化SOC以及我们可以做到的
see here is that that loop doesn't
看到这里是那个循环不
translate to let's do one integer at a
转换为让我们在一个整数
time but we have these sorry we have
时间，但我们有这些抱歉，我们有
these vectorize instructions that
这些向量化指令
basically say read 128 bits that's 4
基本上说读取128位是4
integers into one register 4 integers
整数到一个寄存器4个整数
into another register that's eight
到另一个八的寄存器中
different integers into registers then
然后将不同的整数存入寄存器
do vector ads of those and loop around
做那些广告并循环
eventually they'll add the vector adds
最终他们将添加矢量
together so it's a nice vectorization
在一起，这是一个很好的向量化
optimization by the way most je viens
通过最有效的方式进行优化
will do this hotspot will do this rjv
会做这个热点会做这个rjv
and will do this this is less where it's
并会做到这一点，这是少
been around for a long time right simple
很久很久很简单
that's exactly what vectors are good for
这正是向量的优点
loops on arrays and things like that
循环数组之类的事情
right but if we look at exactly the same
是的，但是如果我们看完全一样的话
thing than your hardware here's a broad
比您的硬件更重要的是
wall mesh
墙网
it's got vector instructions that are
它有矢量指令
twice as wide and here you know our jet
两倍宽，在这里您知道我们的喷气式飞机
compiler for example will recognize that
例如，编译器会认识到
this is capable of doing that and
这有能力做到这一点，
generate instructions that are both
生成既是
twice as wide but even more importantly
两倍宽，但更重要的是
there's instructions that load and add
有加载和添加的说明
in one instruction rather than to
在一个指令中而不是
separate load and add instructions so
分开加载并添加说明，以便
we're giving a lot more integers per
我们给每一个更多的整数
iteration of the loop
循环的迭代
AVX two instructions on broad will also
AVX的两个说明也很广泛
get to execute two of these per cycle
每个周期执行两次
which is more than before so we get much
比以前更多了，所以我们得到了很多
faster so those are nice demonstrations
更快，所以这些都是不错的示范
are just simple vectors and what we
只是简单的向量，我们
could do with them but simple vectors
可以处理它们，但简单的向量
are a little boring because yeah how men
有点无聊，因为是的，男人
do you just sum this stuff in an array
你只是把这些东西汇总成一个数组
what if you're searching for something
如果您正在寻找东西怎么办
and what if you only want to add certain
如果您只想添加某些内容
numbers together what if you stuck in if
数字在一起，如果你坚持如果
in your loop so this is a good example
在您的循环中，这是一个很好的例子
where I'm running on the array but I'm
我在阵列上运行的位置，但我在
only gonna add the even numbers I test
只会加上我测试的偶数
the number if it's even then I'll add it
如果是偶数，我将其添加
otherwise skip it now this presents a
否则，现在跳过它会出现一个
problem for vectors because we don't
向量的问题，因为我们没有
want to add everything we only want to
想添加我们只想添加的所有内容
add stuff selectively and only if it
仅在有选择地添加内容时
matches if we look at what a traditional
匹配，如果我们看看传统
JIT would do with that we get this code
JIT会做到这一点，我们得到此代码
you can actually see it kind of unrolls
你实际上可以看到它的展开
the code the logic twice but it's
代码两次逻辑，但是
literally take the integer test it skip
从字面上接受它跳过的整数测试
it if it's not even do the add and if
如果它甚至没有做添加，如果
there's two of those per loop but
每个循环有两个，但是
there's no vectorization here at all why
这里根本没有向量化，为什么
because there's an F right we can't just
因为有一个F权利，我们不能只是
blindly go do this well a V x2 in x86
盲目地去做这件事x86中的V x2
added a really cool capability to
增加了一个非常酷的功能
vectors it's a masking capability and
向量是一种掩盖能力，
here's what we get with our latest JIT
这就是我们最新的JIT所提供的
the Falcon JIT that we have in Xing this
我们在Xing中拥有的Falcon JIT
is the same code but it Maps and
是相同的代码，但它映射并
recognizes it's running on avx2 capable
认识到它正在支持avx2的系统上运行
hardware and what it actually does is
硬件及其实际作用是
this this code has four interleaved
此代码有四个交错
striped sets of operations but there are
条带化的操作集，但有
no branches in here it loads the data
没有分支在这里加载数据
and then tests all the data in a vector
然后测试向量中的所有数据
and then uses the result of that test
然后使用该测试的结果
mask loads to mask ads and to mask
屏蔽负载以屏蔽广告和屏蔽
stores so only the cells that actually
因此只存储实际
had a yes in them are actually applied
在其中有一个是实际应用
in the vector because the instructions
在向量中，因为指令
cannot do that and because the
无法做到这一点，因为
instructions can now do that we get to
指示现在可以做到
run about six times faster in the loop
在循环中运行大约快六倍
and it just kind of impressive now this
现在，这令人印象深刻
is avx2 you know that was latest
是avx2，您知道这是最新的
greatest until a few months ago the
直到几个月前最大
latest greatest now is skylake which
现在最伟大的是天空湖
goes to avx-512 it's twice again it's
转到avx-512，它再次出现两次
512 bits as a vector that's a lot of
512位向量是很多
hints right so it's 64 bytes it's 16
提示正确，所以它是64字节，它是16
integers in a single vector instruction
单个向量指令中的整数
this is what the same code looks like on
这是相同代码的样子
the latest Scylla care speeds and the
最新的Scylla护理速度和
Google engine I did that this morning
我今天早上做了的Google引擎
this loop performs 64 elements per
此循环每个执行64个元素
iteration of the loop the processor is
处理器的循环迭代
super scalar and will execute two of
超标量，将执行两个
those instructions per cycle and the
每个周期的指令以及
impressive thing about this is I clocked
令人印象深刻的事情是我计时
how fast this goes this specific loop
这个特定循环的速度有多快
runs at about 16 or 17 billion
大约有16或170亿
operations per second on a CPU that's
CPU的每秒操作数
running at 2.3 gigahertz
以2.3 GHz的频率运行
when I say billion operations I mean
当我说十亿操作时
billion ads per second and if you think
每秒十亿个广告，如果您认为
about what's involved in a single ad you
关于单个广告中涉及的内容
have to go around the loop that's an
必须绕过一个循环
operation just you know
你知道的操作
well count don't run the loop test load
好计数不要运行循环测试负载
the integer test the integer decide
整数测试整数决定
whether or not to do something about the
是否对
integer I'm reading the code there right
整数我正在阅读代码
you know and then add that integer to a
你知道然后把那个整数加到
sum and and store it into the other
求和并存储到另一个
array you're looking at a total of
您正在查看的数组
something like 8 or 9 separate logical
像8或9个独立逻辑
operations per iteration and we're
每次迭代的操作，我们
running on a CPU that's doing 2.3
在运行2.3的CPU上运行
gigahertz but it's adding about 17
千兆赫，但它增加了约17
billion of these per second it's all
每秒十亿个
because vectors exists and it's all
因为向量存在而这一切
because the instructions in there and
因为那里的说明和
were able to match the code to the CPU
能够将代码与CPU匹配
and say oh that and you sleepy you could
然后说哦，你困了，你可以
do even better
做得更好
so this is giving a feel for what modern
所以这给人一种现代感
hardware can do at the end this comes
硬件最终可以做到这一点
down to one really simple thing take
归结为一件非常简单的事情
this thing and make it faster
这个东西，并使其更快
right so faster code means lift that
对，所以更快的代码意味着解除
right side of the thing right go faster
事情的右边走得更快
that's most of what better hardware
这就是更好的硬件的大部分
better optimization all those will give
所有这些都会带来更好的优化
us so because that's usually the things
我们这样，因为通常就是这些
most people are interested and I'm gonna
大多数人都感兴趣，我要
get into some specific compiler
进入一些特定的编译器
optimizations and we're done with the
优化，我们已经完成了
machine code if you're leaving because
机器代码（如果要离开的话），因为
of the machine code you can come back
你可以回来的机器代码
I'm gonna start with very simple
我将从非常简单的开始
compiler optimization sort of the ABCs
ABC的编译器优化排序
and build up from there you don't need
并从那里建立不需要的东西
any background for this release so let's
此发行版的任何背景，让我们
start with simple compiler tricks the
从简单的编译器技巧开始
compiler is allowed to take your code
允许编译器接受您的代码
and morph it to something that is
并将其变形为
logically equivalent that is
在逻辑上等效
semantically doing the same thing and as
在语义上做同样的事情
long as the same thing it's allowed to
只要允许同样的事情
execute it that way so let's take stupid
这样执行，让我们变得愚蠢
code here stupid code what can the
这里的代码愚蠢的代码可以
compiler do to this for example it could
例如，编译器可以这样做
change the order of operations it
改变操作顺序吧
doesn't have to do them in the order you
不必按照您的顺序进行操作
wrote them as long as you can't perceive
只要你看不到就写
the difference I can move that and that
我可以移动的那个和那个的区别
that line around you I can also take a
你周围的那条线我也可以
code that has no effect on my result in
对我的结果没有影响的代码
killing that's what called what's called
杀死那就是所谓的
dead code so for example that line
无效代码，例如该行
there's nothing whether I run it or not
无论我是否运行都没有
does not affect the result the compiler
不会影响编译器的结果
figures this out and doesn't do it you
弄清楚这并没有做你
can't measure whether I did it or not so
无法衡量我是否这样做
I don't do it it's fast really really
我不这样做真的真的很快
fast do not do it I can also take values
快不做我也可以取值
and propagate them across operations
并在操作中传播它们
rather than do them the way you wrote
而不是像你写的那样做
them so for example I can take that and
他们，例如，我可以接受和
translate it to this code I don't
将其翻译成我没有的代码
actually have to create temporary
实际上必须创建临时
variables put things in them put them
变量把东西放进去
back at the end you don't need them
最后，您不需要它们
they're gonna get thrown away I could
他们会被扔掉，我可以
just do the math and within that math I
只是做数学，在那个数学里我
could also simplify the math see the
也可以简化数学，请参阅
plus y minus y so I can just say that's
加y减y所以我只能说
X plus X it's a very simple people
X加X这是一个非常简单的人
optimization of that code it's not very
该代码的优化不是很好
smart code compiler will do that
智能代码编译器会做到这一点
not this and virtually all compilers are
不是这个，实际上所有编译器都是
gonna do that for you any compiler that
会为您做任何编译器
you told to try to optimize so it's it's
你被告知要尝试优化，就是这样
not rare to see this kind of stuff now
现在看到这种东西并不稀奇
let's look at a few more tricks
让我们看看一些技巧
propagation of information of data of
传播数据信息
computations can actually affect flow so
计算实际上可以影响流量，因此
take this example here's a piece of code
以这个例子为例
we have an if if this value is big u we
如果这个值很大，我们有一个if
do something if it's small we do
做一些小事，我们做
something else but we know that the
其他的东西，但我们知道
value is 5 the compiler is allowed to
值为5，允许编译器执行
take that code and simplify it to this
采取该代码并将其简化为此
because it's 5 the first part of the if
因为它是if的第一部分
won't happen the second part of that if
如果第二部分不会发生
means bias is 1 we return bias well that
表示偏差为1，我们可以很好地返回偏差
means we return 1 we don't actually have
表示我们返回1我们实际上没有
to execute any of that stuff that's
执行其中的任何东西
propagation of a value that affects
影响值的传播
whether or not I even do flow and I kill
我是否会流动并杀死
part of the code because of it in
部分代码，因为它在
propagating optimizations we can also
传播优化，我们也可以
cache reads if I read something from a
如果我从
field from an array I don't have to read
数组中的字段，我不必阅读
it every time you wrote to read it I
每次您写来阅读它时，我
could read it once and use it many times
可以阅读一次并多次使用
for example if I have this code that
例如，如果我有这段代码
says read a XY z-- I'm allowed to
说读XY z-我被允许
effectively read a dot X once into a
有效地将点X一次读入一个
temporary and use it multiple times now
临时并现在多次使用
this seems like a simple ok I'll get a
这似乎很简单，我会得到一个
little bit win for this but let's take
为此赢得一点点，但让我们
this to them to a higher level what if
对他们来说，如果更高
we have this loop and you know that that
我们有这个循环，你知道
read can be cached you know I'm running
可以缓存读取，您知道我正在运行
a loop as long as the flag is not set
只要未设置标志就循环
but I read the flag once and I don't
但是我读过一次国旗，但我没有
read it again so what's gonna happen
再读一遍，那会发生什么
even if you set the flag that's an
即使您将标志设置为
infinite loop this is what the word
无限循环这就是这个词
volatile is for well that means do not
volatile是很好的，这意味着不要
cache this read I really mean that you
缓存此读取，我的意思是你
need to read it every time around the
需要每次阅读
loop don't do that right but without it
循环不正确，但没有它
you'll get a really fast infinite loop
你会得到一个非常快速的无限循环
there's a lot of things per second but
每秒有很多东西，但是
you never get out rights can be
你永远不会失去权利
eliminated so for example you take these
消除了，例如你拿这些
operations and they write into a dot X 3
操作并将其写入点X 3
times well I just have to do the last
很好，我只需要做最后一件事
write I don't actually
写我实际上不是
have to do all of them cuz maybe I could
必须全部做，因为我可能
do them so fast you can't see the
他们做得这么快，你看不到
difference here's really fast you can't
差异真的很快，你不能
see the difference you can't claim
看到您无法主张的区别
that's wrong cuz you're nuts I could be
错了，因为你疯了，我可能会
so fast you would never see between
如此之快，你将永远不会看到
those instructions so if extras I never
这些指示，所以如果我没有其他
did them so that's a valid optimization
做了他们，所以这是一个有效的优化
and you could do this to a much larger
你可以做的更大
power take this operation that says
采取这种行动，说
let's do a million writes think it throw
让我们做一百万写认为它抛出
away the loop it's not just three
走出循环不只是三个
operations I can get rid of I could take
我可以摆脱的操作
a loop away if the next write I could
如果下一次写我可以循环
take the entire loop away and the writes
带走整个循环并进行写入
in the loop away if after the loop I
在循环中，如果循环后我
write on to it again I could run that
再次写它，我可以运行它
loop really really fast see how fast I
循环真的非常快，看看我有多快
run it zero time so you're not observing
零时间运行它，所以您不会观察
the intermediate values okay those are
中间值还可以
nice simple things now let's look at
好简单的事情现在让我们来看一下
inlining inlining is a very powerful
内联是非常强大的
optimization in fact inlining is
实际上，内联的优化是
probably the most powerful thing
可能是最强大的东西
optimizers do not because of the
优化器不会因为
inlining itself not the removal of the
内联自身而不是去除
overhead of calling something it's
调用它的开销
because when you're in line code you get
因为当您使用行代码时，您会得到
to apply all these other cool techniques
应用所有其他酷技术
on a wider scope let's take an example
在更广泛的范围内，让我们举个例子
simple example of inlining here's a
内联的简单示例
final method that I now won't change its
我现在将不会更改其最终方法
route it returns X and Here I am calling
路由返回X，我在这里打电话
something to get X are simple getter
得到X的东西很简单
compiler can simply say I don't need to
编译器可以简单地说我不需要
call a method for this all just taxes X
为此调用所有方法X
X's are fast we don't actually make a
X很快，我们实际上并没有
calls with them but let's look at how
跟他们打来电话，但让我们看一下
this plays with other things here's a
这和其他东西一起玩
similar method to what I had before but
与我以前使用的方法类似，但
this time I don't know what value is
这次我不知道有什么价值
it's a parameter so I can't optimize
这是一个参数，所以我无法优化
this method and throw away half of it or
此方法并丢弃其中一半或
propagate anything in it because I don't
传播其中的任何东西，因为我不
know what's coming in
知道会发生什么
however the caller is passing five if I
但是如果我的话，来电者会通过5
inline that method at the call site I
在呼叫站点上内联该方法
can optimize it to this if I don't
可以优化它，如果我不这样做
inline it I actually have to run all
内联它实际上我必须全部运行
that code in lining is what makes it
衬里的代码就是它的原因
possible to optimize away most of the
可以优化大部分
code in a called function and this goes
调用函数中的代码，然后
very deep you'll see JIT compilers
很深入，您会看到JIT编译器
inlining dying nine deep to get this
内在垂死的九个深处得到这个
kind of up to
最多
across a very wide scope okay so there's
范围很广，所以有
always simple steps you know nice simple
总是很简单的步骤，你知道很简单
pretty much all compilers will do these
几乎所有的编译器都会做这些
nothing special two Jet's actually I'm
没什么特别的两架喷气式飞机，实际上我是
going to take a little sidetrack here
这里要走一点路
into micro benchmarking just to ruin
进入微基准测试只是毁了
your day if you think you can measure
如果您认为自己可以衡量自己的一天
this stuff easily let's look at some
这些东西很容易让我们看一些
simple loops and measure how fast they
简单的循环并测量它们的速度
are here's a really simple loop you know
这是一个非常简单的循环
that's my benchmark is run this thing in
那是我的基准运行
all time how long it takes it adds it
一直花费多长时间
does it adds basically there's a plus
它是否增加了基本上有一个加号
plus in time so right however many count
加上时间很对，但是很多
times I tell to do so turns out that
我告诉我这样做的时间证明
this code is really really really fast I
这段代码真的真的非常快我
mean if I measure how fast this goes it
意思是如果我衡量这进行得有多快
goes that fast that is impossibly fast
走得快得快
well something is weird here when you
好吧，当你在这里有些奇怪
get numbers there this I faster by three
得到数字，我快三倍
orders of advice six order of magnitude
咨询数量级六个数量级
than the frequency of the CPU that
比CPU的频率
problem means it isn't do any of this
问题意味着它什么都不做
code it's just figured out you don't
代码，只是发现您没有
need to run it so why is it so fast
需要运行它，为什么它这么快
well not quite sure obviously an
好吧，不太清楚
optimization happened we don't want to
优化发生了我们不想
have happen if we want to count how fast
如果我们想计算多快发生了
we loop right oh so nobody uses the sum
我们循环正确哦，所以没人用总和
right okay so let's fix that actually
好吧，让我们实际修复
let's let's do two tries to fix this is
让我们做两个尝试来解决这个问题
let's make it more complicated in the
让我们使其更加复杂
loop I'll add I rather than add one
循环，我将添加而不是添加一个
maybe that'll help turns out that's
也许那会帮助证明
still impossible fast right and that's
快速仍然是不可能的，那是
because this is provably dead code to
因为这证明是死代码
your point nobody uses the sum this is a
您的观点没有人使用总和，这是一个
void net function it has no side effects
无效的净功能，它没有副作用
I've said the function I can immediately
我说过我可以立即使用的功能
return I don't need to run this loop
返回我不需要运行此循环
that's why it's so fast so how do we fix
这就是为什么它这么快所以我们该如何解决
it we return sum right so let's do that
我们返回正确的总和，所以我们这样做
now we have public long this and now
现在我们已经很久很久了
we're returning some propagating the
我们将返回一些传播
thing so we have to do the math right so
事情，所以我们必须做正确的数学运算
is that better well it's still
更好吗，它仍然
impossibly fast and and why is that
太快了，为什么呢？
it turns out the compiler is smart
事实证明编译器很聪明
enough to know that if you do that loop
足以知道如果您执行该循环
sum will be equal to count it doesn't
总和等于不等于
have to run a loop to figure this out
必须运行一个循环来解决这个问题
right great
太好了
so let's complicate it and make it
让我们使其复杂化
harder let's make it do some actual math
更难的是让它做一些实际的数学运算
rather than just add one as many times
而不是只加一遍
as count well add I and all that so is
算是好吧，加我，所有这些都是
that better well it turns out that it is
更好的结果是
better because then now you're gonna
更好，因为那时候你要
time a loop on previous JIT compilers
在以前的JIT编译器上计时
unfortunately JIT compilers are getting
不幸的是，JIT编译器越来越
better for example our latest falcon
更好的例如我们最新的猎鹰
looks at that code and says that's an
看那个代码，说那是
arithmetic series I know how to do that
算术级数我知道该怎么做
math and it figures out that it's count
数学，它算出它是计数
times count minus one over two and
乘以负一乘二，然后
doesn't do the loop and then you can
不做循环，那么你可以
also say let's make it more complicated
还说让我们变得更复杂
in some other way and you know you go
以其他方式，你知道你走了
run this thing times I instead of plus I
运行这个东西，而不是我
and turns out that you can propagate the
并证明您可以传播
zero and show that the loop doesn't
零并显示循环不
happen there's a lot of things that'll
发生的事情很多
kill your loops I'm just trying to show
杀死你的循环我只是想展示
you here and right now right now the
你在这里，现在现在
code I writes to make loops happen looks
我编写的使循环发生的代码看起来
like this and it's important to point
这样，重要的是要指出
that it's right now because somebody's
现在是因为有人
gonna read this slide make an optimize
要阅读这张幻灯片进行优化
let's say I know what he's doing
假设我知道他在做什么
there's only seven or eight possible
可能只有七八种
options for how this goes we're gonna
如何进行选择，我们将
write something that figures out what
写一些可以弄清楚什么的东西
you know what the modulus counties and
你知道模数县和
what the answer is right so we can
答案是正确的，所以我们可以
always have compilers defeat the code
总是让编译器破坏代码
later they get smarter in fact this
后来他们变得更聪明
thing about the arithmetic series we
关于算术级数的事情
didn't write that we use LVM and some
没有写我们使用LVM和一些
smart guy decided to optimizing
聪明的人决定优化
arithmetic series add addition is
算术级数加法为
interesting I don't know why I mean it
有趣，我不知道为什么
mean it the only use of that is to kill
意味着它唯一的用途是杀死
benchmarks right but you know academics
基准是正确的，但您知道学者
do a lot of cool things we get to
做很多很酷的事情
inherit them right okay so that was our
正确地继承它们，所以那是我们的
detour into micro benchmarking and what
绕过微观基准测试以及什么
are the takeaways well Mike we're in
是我们在外卖的麦克吗
checking is hard your write code you try
检查很难，您尝试编写代码
to measure how fast something is you put
衡量你放东西的速度
a loop around it maybe you're not doing
围绕它的循环可能您没有在做
too something and and you may not be
太多的东西，你可能不会
measuring what you think you're doing
衡量自己在做什么
you may be measuring some other side
你可能正在测量另一面
effect like entering the function and
效果就像进入功能
executing it once or something
一次执行
the trickiness changes over time what
技巧会随着时间而改变
works today may not work tomorrow I just
今天工作可能明天就不能工作
showed you that right and you need to
向您表明这一权利，您需要
basically sanity check and check
基本上是健康检查和检查
everything everything suspect everything
一切都怀疑一切
don't believe the numbers check to see
不相信数字会检查
if they make sense very them if you do
如果他们说得通的话
twice the work that you take twice as
工作量是你的两倍
long right if I double the count and I
好吧，如果我加倍计数，我
get the same perfect at the same time
同时获得相同的完美
probably something wrong and if you
可能是错误的，如果你
really want to do this well then use
真的想做得好然后使用
tools that do it well gmh is a really
出色的工具gmh确实是
cool tool for doing micro benchmarks so
做微基准测试的好工具
ugh ugh ugh that's your takeaway but
嗯，那是你的外卖，但是
even if you use J mates you still need
即使您使用J队友，您仍然需要
to suspect everything why all the
怀疑一切，为什么所有
benchmarks are just showed you will run
基准测试表明您将运行
with jmh J which doesn't help you not
与jmh J帮不上忙
have these mistakes it little helps you
有这些错误，对您没有多大帮助
not have other mistakes but everything I
没有其他错误，但我的一切
just showed you was measured with J
刚刚表明您是用J测量的
image it's just optimizer optimized
图像，它只是优化程序优化的
stuff away ok let's get back to some
好了，让我们回到一些
compiler tricks how are we doing on time
编译器提示我们如何按时完成
I've got a few minutes good speculative
我有几分钟的投机性
things JIT compilers in run times get to
JIT编译器在运行时得到的东西
do things you can't do
做你做不到的事情
statically the main thing is you can
静态地主要是你可以
speculate you can actually decide to say
推测您实际上可以决定说
I want to believe something is true and
我想相信某些事情是真的，
I'll optimize the code assuming it's
我会优化代码，假设它是
true but I can't prove it's true if it
是的，但是我不能证明它是真的
stops being true I'll throw the code
不再是真的，我会抛出代码
away but as long as it remains true I
离开，但只要它是真的，我
get to run fast code that is incorrect
开始运行不正确的快速代码
under certain conditions but since I'm
在某些情况下，但由于我
checking the conditions I can run it you
检查条件，我可以运行它
cannot do that in a static optimization
在静态优化中无法做到这一点
so let's take examples of that simple
让我们以简单的例子
untaken path right so I've got this
正确的道路，所以我有这个
method I get a value coming in I don't
方法我获得了价值，但我没有
know what the value is what can I do
知道价值是我能做什么
about that well I can profile this and
关于那好，我可以对此进行剖析
saying you know I've been running this a
说你知道我一直在运行这个
million times and I've never seen a
百万次，我从未见过
value greater than 10 I want to believe
值大于10我想相信
that it'll never be greater than 10
永远不会大于10
let's do this code now I have to
让我们现在执行以下代码
validate my assumption in the code in
在以下代码中验证我的假设
this case right but I basically say if
这种情况对，但我基本上是说
it's greater than thin just don't run
它比薄更大，只是不运行
this uncommon trap go run the interpret
这个罕见的陷阱去运行解释
instead but if it's not then we have an
相反，如果不是，那么我们有一个
optimization for you there's a valid
为您优化有一个有效的
question I could have done an if there
问题我可以做一个如果
and put other optimized code that went
并放入其他经过优化的代码
without a way but once you do this
没有办法，但是一旦你这样做
combinatoric Li the code exponent gets
组合李代码指数得到
slow uncommon traps and ways of not even
缓慢的不常见陷阱和什至不
thinking about the code not generating
考虑代码不生成
and killing it assuming it will never
并假设它永远不会杀死它
happen and then dealing with really slow
发生然后处理非常缓慢
ways if it does happen another cool
如果真的发生的话另一种酷
example is implicit mal checks in Java
示例是Java中的隐式恶意检查
every access to every field in every
每个领域的每个领域的每一次访问
array it requires the JVM to go do that
数组，它需要JVM去执行
when you say get that field from exit
当你说从出口获得那个领域
actually means check that foo is not
实际上意味着检查foo是否不是
null and if it's not null then go do
null，如果不为null，请执行
this every single place you do that and
在每个地方都这样做
if we actually did that every time that
如果实际上每次
would be slow so the JVM wants to
会很慢，所以JVM想
believe you don't give it an ounce to
相信你不会给
follow once to believe that can't prove
跟随一次，相信无法证明
it sometimes you give us nails but what
有时候你给我们钉子，但是
it does is it generates the code is if
它是不是生成了代码，如果
it's not gonna be now what could happen
现在不会发生什么了
well can give us a null and we're gonna
可以给我们一个空，我们要
take a seg vien crash well the JVM
很好地解决JVM崩溃问题
intercepts this ugly says where did it
拦截这个丑陋的说，它在哪里做
happen it happened there I should have
发生在我应该有的地方
had an if there let's like act like
有一个，如果有，让我们喜欢
you're had an if there that works great
你是否有一个很棒的作品
it's really really powerful as an
它确实非常强大
optimization but when you do have an all
优化，但当您拥有全部
it's like a hundred thousand times
大概十万次
slower than doing that if so if you run
如果这样做的话，比这样做要慢
into that code and see a lot of times
进入该代码并看到很多次
where that one throws a
那一个扔一个
nullpointerexception
空指针异常
you basically change the code back to
您基本上将代码更改回
this through the old code away and put
通过旧代码将其丢弃
this back it's an example of a specular
这是镜面反射的一个例子
adaptive optimization class arcane
自适应优化类奥术
analysis is a really strong optimization
分析是非常强大的优化
and it basically takes this approach
它基本上采用这种方法
right now in the world I can see classes
现在在世界上我可以看到课程
have this relationship I can't prove
有这种关系我无法证明
that'll be true in the future but unless
将来会如此，但除非
that changes I can optimize certain
我可以优化某些变化
things here's a concrete example of that
这是一个具体的例子
remember I showed you the in lining and
记得我给你看过衬里
a final method that's ugly to have to
最后的方法很丑陋
put fine on methods just to make them go
完善方法以使它们走
fast and you don't have to do that
速度很快，您不必那样做
here's that same method without final on
这是相同的方法，没有最终决定
it this is an animal this is how you get
这是动物，这就是你如何得到
a color from an animal there are dogs
来自动物的颜色有狗
and cats and birds but none of them have
和猫和鸟，但它们都没有
overridden this mess
覆盖了这个烂摊子
in the current universe so if I have
在目前的宇宙中，如果我有
that caller calling this and I can prove
那个打电话的人，我可以证明
that there's only one implementer of
只有一个实施者
animal get color I can inline it no
动物变色我可以内联它不
conditions no checks no nothing when
条件不检查什么都没有
does this stop being true when you load
加载时，这是否停止为真？
a class that breaks my assumptions so
一门课打破了我的假设
we'll check every time we load a class
每次上课时我们都会检查
whether the assumptions are still true I
假设是否仍然正确
don't have to slow the code down if I
如果我不需要放慢代码
load a chameleon and the chameleon
加载变色龙和变色龙
computes the color based on the branch
根据分支计算颜色
it's sitting on now I have to
现在我必须坐在
implementers and I have to throw away
实施者，我必须扔掉
this optimization and run it with the
此优化并使用
actual virtual potentially so this by
实际的虚拟可能因此
the way is why getters and setters are
这就是为什么吸气剂和二传手是
fast in Java it's why you can write
Java速度很快，这就是为什么您可以编写
clean object-oriented code without this
没有这个的干净的面向对象的代码
optimization you'd have ugly code or
优化你会有丑陋的代码或
you'd be exposing your fields or your do
你会暴露你的领域或你的工作
final getters without overrides and he
最终的吸气剂没有替代，他
can't write chameleons this lets you
不能写变色龙，这让你
write clean object-oriented code that is
编写干净的面向对象的代码
really fast very powerful now what if I
真的很快非常强大现在如果我
had a chameleon so I got this chameleon
有一个变色龙所以我得到了这个变色龙
and now I've got a virtual method I
现在我有了一个虚拟方法
can't do that thing but you know what
不能做那件事，但你知道
yeah there's a chameleon in there dogs
是的，那里有一只变色龙
and cats but the code I'm running in is
和猫，但是我正在运行的代码是
a dog kennel and for some reason people
狗窝，由于某种原因人们
have never put a chameleon in the dog
从来没有在狗身上放过变色龙
kennel so this loop that I'm running has
狗窝，所以我正在运行的循环
never seen anything other than a dog we
除了狗我们再也没有见过
profiled that we figure it out and we
剖析了我们找出答案，然后
generate this code if it's not a dog I
如果不是狗，则生成此代码
don't know what to do here just go
不知道在这里做什么
around the interpreter but if it's a dog
周围的口译员，但如果是狗
boom optimize the heart of it no calls
繁荣优化了它的心脏
it's not as fast as I don't even have to
它没有我什至没有那么快
check but it's really really fast
检查，但是真的非常快
compared to a virtual call and I get to
与虚拟通话相比，我可以
in line and optimize everything in the
并优化一切
method which I can't do if it's a
如果它是我不能做的方法
virtual call okay so all these cool
虚拟通话好，这些都很酷
things were there cool things
那里有很棒的东西
speculative things there's a whole list
投机的东西有一个完整的列表
of additional speculations but
其他猜测，但
speculation depends on something very
投机取决于非常
important that the JVM has to be able to
重要的是，JVM必须能够
do it's the optimization we're
这是我们的优化
optimizing based on assumptions that are
根据以下假设进行优化
not provable they're observed we're
无法证明他们被观察到
hoping that they're true
希望他们是真的
we really hope they're true but often
我们真的希望他们是真实的，但经常
they won't be so we have to be able to
他们不会，所以我们必须能够
take the code we generated throw it away
把我们生成的代码丢掉
go back to this other code slow code and
回到其他代码慢代码，然后
go again that's what the optimization is
再来一次，这就是优化
without the optimizations you do not get
没有优化，您将无法获得
to do speculations like this so first
要做这样的推测
you need to be able to be optimized and
您需要能够进行优化，
remember this picture the reason this is
记住这张照片的原因是
not a smooth yellow to green to blue
黄色到绿色到蓝色都不平滑
thing and we have spikes going in there
东西，我们那里有尖峰
is because sometimes our optimizations
是因为有时我们的优化
are wrong
错了
sometimes we speculate we find out we're
有时我们推测我们发现自己
wrong we have to throw away the code go
错误的，我们必须扔掉代码去
back to the yellow or green and go again
回到黄色或绿色，然后再走一次
that's where you have these spikes where
那就是这些尖峰的地方
it was blue but that went back to green
它是蓝色的，但是又变回绿色
or yellow and back again eventually
或黄色，并最终再次返回
it'll stabilize it'll learn it'll
它会稳定它会学习它
speculate that was wrong it'll stabilize
推测是错误的它将稳定
and only have the code that survives the
并且只有能够幸存的代码
speculations for a long time so the
长期以来的猜测
optimization is another gnarly thing if
优化是另一回事
you think Michael bench ranking hard
你认为迈克尔替补排名很难
dealing with warm-up and the
处理热身和
optimization is much much harder to
优化要困难得多
figure out especially if you run really
弄清楚，特别是如果你真的跑步
really short benchmarks or really small
基准很短或很小
data sets so the idea is that you know
数据集，所以这个想法是，你知道
often people look at this and say okay
人们常常看着这个说好
that the optimization make me go really
优化使我真正走了
slow how do I warm things up so I won't
慢一点，我怎么热身，所以我不会
have the slow code let's exercise it
有慢代码让我们练习一下
give it some real stuff and then run the
给它一些真实的东西，然后运行
real code the real note I want and the
真实代码我想要的真实音符以及
problem with that is you often think
问题是你经常想
you're warm
你很温暖
but then the behavior of the world
但是世界的行为
changed just the number changed if
只是改变数字，如果
something happened in a packet somewhere
小包中某处发生了什么
our message and suddenly things are not
我们的信息突然间事情变得不顺利
what you thought it right they don't
你认为正确的他们不
have to happen in the first few minutes
必须在前几分钟内发生
they can happen at 3:00 p.m. so many
他们可能在下午3:00发生
many potential causes for the
许多潜在的原因
optimization um the reason warm-up
优化和预热的原因
doesn't cut it is easy to demonstrate
不削减，很容易证明
with the concrete real-world motivation
具有具体的现实世界动机
imagine you're writing a trading system
想象您正在编写交易系统
and it's in Java because you can write
它在Java中，因为您可以编写
fast and go to market fast but when you
快速并快速进入市场，但是当您
trade the market opens and everybody
交易市场开放，每个人
rushes in in the volatility is high and
急于波动，
that's where most of the cool stuff is
那是最酷的东西所在的地方
happening and you just started your JVM
发生了，您刚刚启动了JVM
and you running into
而你遇到
credit code and it's still profiling so
信用代码，它仍然在分析
you want to warm it up you want to
你想热身，你想
before you start this you're gonna
在开始这个之前，你要
you're gonna run stuff we'll say okay
你会跑东西，我们会说好的
you know what I don't want to wait for
你知道我不想等什么
10,000 operations to happen before I get
在我得到10,000次操作之前
off to mice code let's run prime it with
鼠标代码，让我们运行它
you know 20,000 traffic things fake
你知道20,000件假货
traffic that maybe I recorded yesterday
我昨天记录的流量
exercise the codes so it's nice and
练习代码，这样很好
ready for the first transaction at
准备在进行第一笔交易
market open and it's already warm or
市场开放，已经很热
teach it it and it does that right so
教它，它做对了，所以
you warm it up to just go a while they
你热身只是去他们一会儿
speculate they figure out the wrong they
推测他们弄错了
do whatever it is they settle but what
不管他们解决了什么，做什么
actually happens here what you're doing
实际上发生在这里你在做什么
is running fake traffic through you
正在通过您进行虚假流量
don't actually mean to do 20,000 trades
其实并不意味着要进行20,000笔交易
right with somebody else's money so
用别人的钱吧
usually the fake logic has something in
通常，假逻辑中包含某些内容
it that says go to the other but but
它说去另一个但
it's fake so don't really send it what
这是假的，所以不要真正发送它
is the JIT compiler gonna optimize for
JIT编译器将针对以下内容进行优化
it's gonna optimize for not trading
它会针对不交易进行优化
because it's run twenty thousand things
因为运行了两万件事
that it's never traded maybe this never
从来没有交易过，也许从来没有
happens and what happens in the first
发生和第一次发生的事情
straight we do optimized go back to the
直，我们做优化回到
beginning and start collecting stuff
开始并开始收集东西
from scratch right it looks like this
从头开始，它看起来像这样
you warmed it up you know really really
你加热了它，你真的知道
fast the boom market opens you go slow
快速的繁荣市场打开你走慢
again so in reality this warm-up in
再次如此，实际上在这种热身
learning an aggressive optimization
学习积极的优化
happens here the optimization happens
优化发生在这里
here then you re optimized with the real
在这里，您可以使用真实的
knowledge that's kind of the evolution
进化的知识
of things okay that's warmup that's the
好的事情就是热身
optimization what can we do about this
优化我们可以对此做些什么
well one capability we actually built
我们实际建立的一项功能
into a JVM is there build is you log in
进入JVM是否有构建？您是否登录
replay optimizations across runs record
在运行记录中重播优化
the inputs to optimizations from
来自优化的输入
yesterday start today with what we
昨天从今天开始
learned yesterday including what not to
昨天学到的东西包括
do so think of it simply as you tell a
因此，只要您告诉一个
JVM to record why and how it compiled
JVM记录为什么以及如何编译
things and tomorrow you tell the gym to
事情，明天你告诉体育馆
start with that recording it Prime's up
首先从录音开始
it starts everything JIT compiler
它会启动所有的JIT编译器
everything you're ready for the first
一切准备就绪
transaction to go fast rather than 10
交易要快而不是10
thousand people or purchases or trades
千人或购买或交易
going slow before you go fast and you
变慢，然后再变快，然后你
can actually build a workflow that will
实际上可以建立一个工作流程
prove to you that nothing that you
向你证明你没有任何东西
applied yesterday has not yet been
昨天申请还没有
applied the impact of that is to take
应用的影响是
that the optimization and flatten it out
优化并将其展平
you know make it happy but also to take
你知道让它快乐但也要
that warmup time that actually requires
实际需要的预热时间
you to train things and bring that down
您训练事物并将其降低
to practically nothing because you don't
几乎什么都没有，因为你没有
have to run traffic through it you just
必须通过它运行流量
need to initialize things so you get
需要初始化东西，所以你得到
this nice flat operation what does this
这个好的平面操作这是什么
mean to this picture so I already showed
意思是这张照片，所以我已经展示了
you that better ginning raises the bar
你说更好的轧花提高了标准
this brings it over to the left and
这将其移到左侧，
flattens it right you take away all that
把它弄平就可以了
warm-up curve so that's better
预热曲线，这样更好
now what's left here what do we have
现在剩下的还有什么
left to do what's missing this thing
留着做这件事缺少的事情
still drops to zero speed every once in
仍然每次下降到零速度
a while and that's that last component
一会儿，那是最后一个组成部分
what if we could make it not drop to
如果我们不能让它下降到
zero speed every once in a while and
零速不时
then we get this nice flat speed close
然后我们得到这个不错的平速关闭
to what we actually want to see that's
到我们真正想要看到的是
where c4 garbage collector comes and
C4垃圾收集器到那里，
this is the really proud brow you know
这是你真正骄傲的眉头
just beating thing that I get to say c4
只是打我要说的东西c4
in zing JVM you can run any of you have
在zing JVM中，您可以运行任何一个
applications on basically eliminates GC
应用程序基本上消除了GC
as a problem it takes things that look
作为一个问题，它需要看起来像东西
like the thing on the left that glitch
就像左边那个小故障
all the time and they can look like the
一直以来，它们看起来像
thing on the right they only glitch some
在右边的东西，他们只是小故障
of the time those glitches are not
这些时间的故障不是
because of the JVM there are many other
由于JVM，还有许多其他
reasons you clutch we take away the JVM
您紧紧抓住我们的理由
glitch reasons we also take away all the
故障的原因，我们也带走了所有
reason to tune GC so you might have
调整GC的原因，因此您可能有
recognized and some of these flags you
公认，其中一些标志
might be doing these sometimes you want
有时您可能想要做这些
to run fast you want to and without
想要快速运行而没有
pauses you want to delay the pauses so
您想延迟一下暂停，这样
you tune things and you need to tune
你调整东西，你需要调整
things right right this application in
对这个应用程序的正确处理
that application diametrically opposed
该应用程序截然相反
values for flag X which means you've
标志X的值，表示您已经
tried a lot of things and you figured
尝试了很多事情，你想通了
out how to tune this for your current
了解如何针对当前情况进行调整
workload if you think those are a lot of
如果您认为这些工作量很大
flags here are a few more flags you can
标志这里还有一些其他标志
choose how to tune any identities the
选择如何调整任何身份
modern way to tune things with us is
与我们调和的现代方式是
this
这个
you give it a big heat and it works now
你给它很大的热量，它现在可以工作
that's a waste
那是浪费
so you shrink the heap and shrink that
所以你缩小堆并缩小
he'd been in shape and you figure out
他一直保持体形，你想通
how small how small you can go before it
你能走多小
breaks you triple the heap and you go
打破你的三倍堆，你去
home that was GC tuning
GC优化的家
today right now in practice I'm thinking
今天在实践中，我在想
not trade like this is Cassandra running
不像卡桑德拉那样交易
on a normal Broadwell machine and that's
在普通的Broadwell机器上，那是
the one milli second passe level running
一毫秒通过级别
under full stress of a benchmark so if
在基准的全部压力下，如果
you care about 400 micro second glitches
你在乎400微秒的毛刺
yeah we do glitch but Linux Fletch is
是的，我们确实有故障，但是Linux Fletch是
bigger than that Cassandra delicious
比Cassandra好吃
bigger your i/o glitch is bigger than
您的I / O故障大于
that this is the noise the rest of the
这是其余的噪音
signal so you know in practice we get to
信号，所以您实际上知道我们可以
do things like this Cassandra an EWS
做这样的事情Cassandra EWS
under an SLA simple question is I need
在SLA下，我需要一个简单的问题
to meet that SLA with that many nodes
用那么多节点满足该SLA
how much traffic can they run through it
他们可以通过多少流量
you run it with hotspot with G one with
你用G一的热点来运行它
two months of consulting of tuning and
两个月的调音和咨询
you get the speed this is an actual real
你得到的速度，这是一个实际的真实
case from an actual customer you run it
来自实际客户的案例，您可以运行它
with zing with no tuning and you get
没有调整就可以得到
that those are real numbers for
这些是实数
Cassandra on AWS today on the latest
今天在AWS上的Cassandra最新
greatest instances now this is not
现在最大的例子不是
because we run the code five times
因为我们运行了五次代码
faster we do run the code about 11%
更快地运行代码约11％
faster and we start up quicker but it
更快，我们启动更快，但是
doesn't affect this this is because you
不会影响这是因为你
can press this thing much harder before
可以更努力地压这东西
the glitches break down something this
小故障打破了这种东西
is about removing glitches and what that
关于消除毛刺以及什么
translates into in reality is things
转化为现实就是事物
like this if you actually monitor load
如果您实际上监视负载，则这样
and timeouts or errors or field success
超时，错误或现场成功
rates which is just what this orange
利率，这就是这个橙色
line is every time it dips that's a
线是每次浸入
failure 100% is a thunk 98% at the
失败100％是重击98％
bottom you get up to 2% failure in this
在此情况下，您最多会失败2％
case you turn it on to zing and it runs
如果您将其打开并运行
smooth you get speed like you want you
顺畅地获得所需的速度
get this kind of speed so that one's me
得到这样的速度，以便成为我
bragging at the end I apologize for that
最后吹牛我为此表示歉意
hopefully the beginning of it was more
希望它的开始更多
educational if you really want to know
具有教育意义，如果您真的想知道
more about it you can come to our booth
有关它的更多信息，您可以到我们的展位
to come talk to me but at this point I
来跟我说话，但在这一点上我
think we're done on time
认为我们按时完成了
I'll be happy to take some Q&amp;A as I wrap
我很高兴在包装时接受一些问答
up and clear the room for the next
并清理下一个房间
speaker and I'll hang around here as
演讲者，我会在这里闲逛
long as you guys want so feel free to
只要你们想要，随时
ask questions while I start wrapping up
当我开始总结时问一些问题
this stuff thank you
这东西谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]